ILGWU International Relations Department publications 5780/062 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 11, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: TWARO (ITGLWF-ARO) Asian Seminar on Free Trade Zones: Part I Texts on Lectures, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    By International Textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation. Tokyo, 6th-13th March 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: TWARO (TTGLWF-ARO) Asian Seminar on Free Trade Zones: Part I Texts of Lectures, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Box: 12, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: Activity Report (1988-1992), Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    By Neil Kearney: General Secretary. Espinho, Portugual. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ITGLWF: The World 6th Congress; The ITGLWF: What is is and what it does, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    By International Textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation. Espinho, Portugual. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: ITGLWF The 7th World Congress: ITGLWF Rules: Proposals for Amendments, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
    By International Textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation. Melbourne, Australia. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: 5th World Congress: Summar of Proceedings, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: Motions For Submission to Congress, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: Motions For Submissions to Congress, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: Sharing Trade Benefits: An ITGLWF Policy Satement on the Future of trade in Textiles and Clothing beyond 1st January 1993, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: The ITGLWF: What it is and what it does, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: Working to Live: An ITGLWF Policy Statement to Mark the Proclamaion of 1994 as the Year of the Family, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: ITGLWF The Wrold 6th Congress: Statements For Submission to Congress, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Box: 12, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: ITGLWF The 6th World Congress: Programme, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: Country Reports 1992, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: ITGLWF The World 6th Congress: Towards 2000: A World Action Programme, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Box: 12, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 6th World Congree, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Espinho, Portugual. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Decisions of Congress, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Financial Reports (1988-1991), Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Box: 12, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Decisions of Congress, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Financial Reports, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: ITGLWF Rules; Proposals for Amendments, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Box: 13, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Mulitnational Corporations and the Trade Unions, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Seminar held in Djakarta, Indonesia. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report on Homework, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Textiles and Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By C. Goudima. Item is in English.
- Box: 13, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A report on the Textile, Clothing and Leather Industries in North Africa, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By K. Eaton. 1. Morroco. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rehabilitation of the Textile Industry; Observations and Recommendations: Preliminary report, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    ATIRA. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Report on Health and Safety in the Textile, Garmet, and Leather industries, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Sandra Dent. 2nd World Congress held in Dublin, Ireland in 1976; ITGLWF based in Brussels. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Trade Unions and the Transnationals, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Information Bulletin. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Twaro.Fes Seminar on FTZ's in Malaysia, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Box: 13, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A report on the Textile, Clothing and leather industries in North Africa, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By K. Eaton. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report of the Trade Union delegation to South America investigating conditions in the clothing and textile industries, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Report on Child Labor, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Textile, Garment and Leather Industries and Trade Unions in 6 French-speaking African countries, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By G. Conan. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Textiles and Clothing Industries, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Box: 13, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A report on the Textile, Clothing and Leather Industries in 3 English-speaking East African Countries, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. 1. Malawi. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Abestos, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: BATA Report, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Colombo, Sri Lanka. 28 November - 7 December 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Report on Shift Work, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The Leading Multination Companies in the Textiles, Garment, and Leather industries, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. First World Congress; Amsterdam Netherlands 1972. Item is in English.
- Box: 13, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: International Year of the Family; ITGLWF Campaign, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. May 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Year of the Family; ITGLWF Campaign, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. For the Press. For Release: Immediate. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Year of the Family; ITGLWF Campaign, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. April 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Autumn 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Autumn 1992. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. June 1992. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. June 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. September 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Winter 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. June 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. Winter 1993. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.3 (1994). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.1 (1994). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.2 (1994). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation Newsletter. no.2 (1995). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation Newsletter. no.2 (1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: ITGLWF Newsletter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.1 (1995). Item is in English.
- Box: 13, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.1 (1984:Jan.). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.1 (1985:July 8). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.15 (1986:Nov. 7). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.12 (1986:Oct. 6). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.4 (1987:Apr. 15). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.18 (1987: Dec. 8). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.13 (1987:July 16). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.6 (1987:May 14). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.2 (1987: Feb. 3). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.17 (1987:Dec. 8). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.1 (1987:Jan. 21). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.12 (1987:July 16). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.2 (1988:Feb. 11). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.1 (1991:Mar. 12). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.2 (1991:Oct.). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Informations. News. Nachrichten., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By International Textile, Garmet and Leather Workers Federation. no.1 (1992:Mar.). Title only in French, English, and German. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: ICFTU Affiliated Organizations; Report on Education Activities, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
    By Japanese Confederation of Labour (Domei). Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: FUSION, Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
    By Fusion Energy Foundation. v.9:no.1 (1987:Jan./Feb.). Japan; Superpower for Progress. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Keidanren Review, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By Keidanran (Japan Federation of Economic Organizations). No. 69 (1981:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Keidanren Review, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By Keidanran (Japan Federation of Economic Organizations). No. 70 (1981:Aug.). Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Profile, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    By JIL (Japan Institute of Labour). Item is in English; Japanese.
- Box: 14, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Tokyo 1994: The Annual Meeting of the Trilateral Commission, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    By The Trilateral Commission. Trialogue: 47. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Opening Japan: Recommendations for a Real World Solution, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Clyde Prestowitz; Lawrence Chimerine, Andrew Szamosszegi. September, 1994; 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Japan Now, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    By the Embassy of Japan. November 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Japan Now, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    By the Embassy of Japan. January 1995. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Revitalizing the Economy: Issues for Employers and Labor, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Committee For The Study Of Labor Issues; Japan Fedreration of Employers' Associations (Nikkeiren). Position Paper 1995. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Labour Unions and Labour-Management Relations, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By Tokuichi Utada. Japanese Industrial Relations Series, no.2. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Awahima Forum: Regional Integration and the Asia-Pacific Economy, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    By The Japan Institute of International Affairs. April 23-24, 1993. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Labour Administration In Japan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    By Ministry of Labour. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Labour-Management Relations in Japan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Labour-Management Relations in Japan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Box: 14, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Japanese Working Life Profile: Labor Statistics, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Japanese Working Life Profile: Labor Statistics, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Japanese Working Life Profile: Statistical Aspects, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Japanese Working Life Profile: Statistical Aspects, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
    By JIL (Japan Institute of Labour). Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: RENGO: Final Report of the Union Offensive, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
    By Japanese Trade Union Confederation. August 1991, No.13. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: JILAF: Japan International Labour Foundation, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
    By Japan International Labour Foundation. pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: JILAF: Making the Earth Rounder, Promoting International Cooperation, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
    By Japan International Labour Foundation. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The 7th Joing Conference of Actwu-Ilgwu-Zensen: North Pacific Rim Textile and Clothing Unions Conference, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
    By ZENSEN (Japanese Federation of Textile, Garment, Chemical, Mercantile, Food and Allied Industries Workers' Unions). March 1992. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Fraternity Hill ZENSEN Education Center, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By ZENSEN (Japanese Federation of Textile, Garment, Chemical, Mercantile, Food and Allied Industries Workers' Unions). 2 copies. Item is in English; Japanese.
- Box: 14, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The American Federationist, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
    By American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations. v.89:no.4 (1982:Apr./June). Japanese Management: Myth or Magic. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: ZENSEN, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
    By ZENSEN (Japanese Federation of Textile, Garment, Chemical, Mercantile, Food and Allied Industries Workers' Unions). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ZENSEN, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Box: 14, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: This is Sohyo: Japanese Workers and Their Struggles, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
    By Sohyo (General Council of Trade Unions of Japan). Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: CGP: The Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership Program Guidelines, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
    By The Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: JET: Japan Exchange and Teaching Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
    By Japanese Exchange and Teaching Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: ZENMIN ROKYO, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
    By Japanese Private Sector Trade Union Council (JPTUC). Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: La OIT En Visperas Del Siglo XXI, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Grupo de los Trabajadores del Consejo de Administracion de la OIT. November, 1993. Photocopy. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 15, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: International Conference on Strategies for Global Labor Solidarity, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By International Union of Food and Allied Workers' Associations North American Regional Organization. July 7-9, 1989. Summary and Related Materials. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Labor Solidarity: The Campaign For Justice For Moses Mayekiso, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Don Stillman. Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bureau of International Labor Affairs: A Brief Outline of Principal Activities, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Free Labour World, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By Luc Demaret; Bernie Russell. no.5 (1991:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Free Trade Union Institute, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By Paul J. Somogyi. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: In the Service of the State: The World Federation of Trade Unions and "International Labor Unity", Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By Free Trade Union Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: International Labor Review, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By ILO. v.127:no.2 (1988:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: International Solidarity in Action IUF/NARO Reports, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By Joy Ann Grune. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Lets Learn About Our International Trade Union Organization, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By PTTI (Postal, Telegraph and Telephone International). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Solidarismo: Corporatism Redux, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By Richard L. Hough. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Solidarismo: Corporatism Redux, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Statutes, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: The Internation Labor Movement: Development and Structure, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By Ruben Rotondaro. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Unity: Inter-American Information Bulletin of PTTI, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: IUF/NARO Reports, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By International Union of Food and Allied Workers' Associations News Bulletin. v.1:no.1 (1989:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: News Bulletion, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By International Union of Food and Allied Workers' Associations. no.5/6 (1989). Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Le defi lance a l'Europe, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    By NFS/DGB. Item is in French.
- Box: 15, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Between the Government and the United States of America, the Government of Canada and the Government of the United Mexican States, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Emerging Patterns of Industrial Relations in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    TWO COPIES. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: EPC: The Social Implications of a North American Free Trade Agreement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Exploiting Both Sides: U.S.- Mexico Free Trade, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: No NAFTA Action Source Book, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: North American Agreement on Labor Cooperation: A Guide, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Not This NAFTA: How would the proposed North American Free Trade Agreement affect you?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Special NAFTA Bulletin: Workers Rights News, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Box: 15, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Regionalism in a Converging World, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
    By Toyoo Gyohten. Discussion Draft for Lisbon Meeting. Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Protection of Workers in Multinational Companies, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Box: 15, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Making the International Connection Work, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    By Industrial Union Department. Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Multinational Monitor, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
    By Multinational Monitor. Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The U.S. Trade Deficit and the Transnational Corporations, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    By World Federation of Trade Unions. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Viewpoint; Multinational Corporations - Trading U.S. Jobs for Coporate Profit, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)